=== TOOLS OFFERED TO THE MODEL (file tools: ls, read_file, write_file, edit_file, delete, glob, grep; shell: execute; subagents: task) ===
 - ls
 - read_file
 - write_file
 - edit_file
 - delete
 - glob
 - grep
 - execute
 - task

=== DESCRIPTION OF THE `task` TOOL (subagents) ===
Launch an ephemeral subagent to handle a complex, multi-step task.

Available agent types and the tools they have access to:
- general-purpose: General-purpose agent for researching complex questions, searching for files and content, and executing multi-step tasks. When you are searching for a keyword or file and are not confident that you will find the right match in the first few tries use this agent to perform the search for you. This agent has access to all tools as the main agent.

Specify subagent_type to select the agent. Usage notes:
- Launch multiple agents concurrently when their tasks are independent, using a single message with multiple tool calls.
- Each invocation is stateless by default: the agent sees only the prompt you give it and returns a single final report. Put full detail in the prompt and state exactly what it should return — unless an agent type below says it inherits your conversation instead.
- The agent's report is not shown to the user; relay a summary yourself.
- Tell the agent whether to create content, analyze, or only research, since it can't necessarily see the user's intent unless it inherits your conversation, as noted per agent type below.
- If an agent's description says to use it proactively, do so without waiting to be asked.
- When only general-purpose is available, use it for any complex, context-heavy task; it has the same capabilities as the main agent.

=== DESCRIPTION OF THE `execute` TOOL (shell) ===
Executes a shell command in an isolated sandbox and returns combined stdout/stderr with the exit code (truncated if very large).

Usage:
- Quote paths containing spaces (e.g. cd "/path/with spaces").
- Chain commands with ';' or '&&' (use '&&' when a command depends on the previous); do not use newlines except inside quoted strings.
- Use absolute paths and avoid `cd` so the working directory stays stable; use the optional timeout to override the default.
- You MUST avoid using search commands like find and grep. Instead use the grep, glob tools to search. Use read_file rather than cat/head/tail.
    - execute(command="find . -name '*.py'")  # Use glob tool instead
    - execute(command="grep -r 'pattern' .")  # Use grep tool instead

Only available on backends implementing SandboxBackendProtocol; otherwise it returns an error.

=== SYSTEM PROMPT (empty unless you pass system_prompt=...) ===
''
